Mast Bhai's friend, thank you, isn't that right,
but bro, its tyre is there and there are no
chances of insects during the rains, isn't it?
Then brother, its insurance is also there for the next
5 years. No tension, no
brother, you know so much, still you have such a
big misunderstanding, this 5
year insurance of yours is for third party
damage, which covers others but
not you, the insurance which covers tomorrow's damage and theft will
expire after just one year, don't
forget to get it renewed every year,
brother
Mithai, you also don't remain under this misunderstanding and get
your two wheeler insurance policy renewed every year from ICICI Lombard
and take advantage
of all the great features like our wide network